[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"], "TIME": ["Last night"]}, "docId": "131209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "-NONE-", "."], "qSentId": 18, "question": "How extreme is it and what can you tell me about this missing family?", "question_tokens": ["How", "extreme", "is", "it", "and", "what", "can", "you", "tell", "me", "about", "this", "missing", "family", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "CC", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 19, "answer": "Last night, Piers, it was 17 degrees below 0.", "answer_tokens": ["Last", "night", ",", "Piers", ",", "it", "was", "17", "degrees", "below", "0", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "NN", "CC", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 36, "question": "Whereabouts are you right now and what are the conditions like?", "question_tokens": ["Whereabouts", "are", "you", "right", "now", "and", "what", "are", "the", "conditions", "like", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "CC", "WP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 37, "answer": "It's just very icy and very cold.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "just", "very", "icy", "and", "very", "cold", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 41, "question": "How are you coping with what has happened and what have the authorities told you about the likelihood that this will end with the recovery of everybody safe and well?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "you", "coping", "with", "what", "has", "happened", "and", "what", "have", "the", "authorities", "told", "you", "about", "the", "likelihood", "that", "this", "will", "end", "with", "the", "recovery", "of", "everybody", "safe", "and", "well", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "CC", "WP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "CC", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 42, "answer": "Everybody has been very positive.", "answer_tokens": ["Everybody", "has", "been", "very", "positive", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 54, "question": "Chad Myers is saying that 17 degrees below -- below normal, what are you experiencing?", "question_tokens": ["Chad", "Myers", "is", "saying", "that", "17", "degrees", "below", "--", "below", "normal", ",", "what", "are", "you", "experiencing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "IN", ":", "IN", "JJ", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 55, "answer": "It's just -- it's extremely cold.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "just", "--", "it", "'s", "extremely", "cold", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Chad Myers"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "NN", ",", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 70, "question": "What was your reaction when you heard that he had finally died?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "your", "reaction", "when", "you", "heard", "that", "he", "had", "finally", "died", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 71, "answer": "I was somewhat surprised because he had such resilience, such determination.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "somewhat", "surprised", "because", "he", "had", "such", "resilience", ",", "such", "determination", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 90, "question": "But the great, great thing about Mandela was that when he came out of prison he could've sought awful revenge on his captors and all that stood by the captors, but he went completely the opposite way, didn't he?", "question_tokens": ["But", "the", "great", ",", "great", "thing", "about", "Mandela", "was", "that", "when", "he", "came", "out", "of", "prison", "he", "could", "'ve", "sought", "awful", "revenge", "on", "his", "captors", "and", "all", "that", "stood", "by", "the", "captors", ",", "but", "he", "went", "completely", "the", "opposite", "way", ",", "did", "n't", "he", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 91, "answer": "We have two things about that.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "have", "two", "things", "about", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mandela"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 120, "question": "Because of all this controversy?", "question_tokens": ["Because", "of", "all", "this", "controversy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 121, "answer": "Well, partly because of the controversy.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "partly", "because", "of", "the", "controversy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 152, "question": "They have the ability to do that, but under our constitution and our set of laws, do they have the right to do that?", "question_tokens": ["They", "have", "the", "ability", "to", "do", "that", ",", "but", "under", "our", "constitution", "and", "our", "set", "of", "laws", ",", "do", "they", "have", "the", "right", "to", "do", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", ",", "CC", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 153, "answer": "That's the big debate.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "the", "big", "debate", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 159, "question": "And how prevalent do you think it may be?", "question_tokens": ["And", "how", "prevalent", "do", "you", "think", "it", "may", "be", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 160, "answer": "Well, first I want to say I'm not an expert on this subject.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "first", "I", "want", "to", "say", "I", "'m", "not", "an", "expert", "on", "this", "subject", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["CBS News"]}, "docId": "131209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "IN", "DT", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 187, "question": "Many people believe there's a double standard at CBS in the way that you were treated in terms of the way you departed from CBS and the way that Lara Logan's been treated, and the way they've handled this crisis, what do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Many", "people", "believe", "there", "'s", "a", "double", "standard", "at", "CBS", "in", "the", "way", "that", "you", "were", "treated", "in", "terms", "of", "the", "way", "you", "departed", "from", "CBS", "and", "the", "way", "that", "Lara", "Logan", "'s", "been", "treated", ",", "and", "the", "way", "they", "'ve", "handled", "this", "crisis", ",", "what", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "VBN", "VBN", ",", "CC", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 188, "answer": "We'll first of all, CBS News has a lot to answer for this.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "'ll", "first", "of", "all", ",", "CBS", "News", "has", "a", "lot", "to", "answer", "for", "this", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["CBS", "CBS"], "PERSON": ["Lara Logan"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 228, "question": "What are you going to do about this?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "you", "going", "to", "do", "about", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 229, "answer": "Well this is really a hardiest movement.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", "this", "is", "really", "a", "hardiest", "movement", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 244, "question": "I guess they are going to guess this, they think code, geeks, you know, people like Jack, you know?", "question_tokens": ["I", "guess", "they", "are", "going", "to", "guess", "this", ",", "they", "think", "code", ",", "geeks", ",", "you", "know", ",", "people", "like", "Jack", ",", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "NN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 245, "answer": "No doubt about that.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "doubt", "about", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jack"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "RP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 254, "question": "Why is there so few American schools that are really investing a lot of time and effort into this?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "is", "there", "so", "few", "American", "schools", "that", "are", "really", "investing", "a", "lot", "of", "time", "and", "effort", "into", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 255, "answer": "I think from my end, it's -- it was hard, you know, when I was growing up to see the value in it.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "from", "my", "end", ",", "it", "'s", "--", "it", "was", "hard", ",", "you", "know", ",", "when", "I", "was", "growing", "up", "to", "see", "the", "value", "in", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "VBZ", "RB", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 261, "question": "What's the link there?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "the", "link", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 262, "answer": "Well there's actually schools that have had every students do computer science in the 9th grade.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", "there", "'s", "actually", "schools", "that", "have", "had", "every", "students", "do", "computer", "science", "in", "the", "9th", "grade", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "NN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 264, "question": "What are the Chinese doing that's so different to the Americans?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "the", "Chinese", "doing", "that", "'s", "so", "different", "to", "the", "Americans", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "DT", "NNPS", "."], "aSentId": 265, "answer": "Well in computer science the difference is that they're teaching it.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", "in", "computer", "science", "the", "difference", "is", "that", "they", "'re", "teaching", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "CD", "NN", "CC", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 276, "question": "Is Zuckerberg going to use Facebook to embrace this very campaign that you're running?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "Zuckerberg", "going", "to", "use", "Facebook", "to", "embrace", "this", "very", "campaign", "that", "you", "'re", "running", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "NNP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "RB", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 277, "answer": "I think it's one channel but, you know, a younger generation is using their mobile device every single day.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "'s", "one", "channel", "but", ",", "you", "know", ",", "a", "younger", "generation", "is", "using", "their", "mobile", "device", "every", "single", "day", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "CC", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "VBN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WP", "VBZ", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 287, "question": "What right really if you collect it we got to say, where we want to defend people's privacy?", "question_tokens": ["What", "right", "really", "if", "you", "collect", "it", "we", "got", "to", "say", ",", "where", "we", "want", "to", "defend", "people", "'s", "privacy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "RB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "POS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 288, "answer": "Well we intend to defend the people using the service and their voice, and make sure that that's protected and they have an understanding of who has access to the information.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", "we", "intend", "to", "defend", "the", "people", "using", "the", "service", "and", "their", "voice", ",", "and", "make", "sure", "that", "that", "'s", "protected", "and", "they", "have", "an", "understanding", "of", "who", "has", "access", "to", "the", "information", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "DT", "RB", "CC", "TO", "PRP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 294, "question": "Is that the short version of your polite letter?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "the", "short", "version", "of", "your", "polite", "letter", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 295, "answer": "I don't know if I can necessarily speak to that specifically but to us it's just establishing trust in people who are using our service and making sure that we maintain that.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "if", "I", "can", "necessarily", "speak", "to", "that", "specifically", "but", "to", "us", "it", "'s", "just", "establishing", "trust", "in", "people", "who", "are", "using", "our", "service", "and", "making", "sure", "that", "we", "maintain", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 301, "question": "You never look at your stock price?", "question_tokens": ["You", "never", "look", "at", "your", "stock", "price", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 302, "answer": "I don't.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 303, "question": "Never?", "question_tokens": ["Never", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 304, "answer": "It's not the leading indicator of success.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "not", "the", "leading", "indicator", "of", "success", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "CD", ",", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 309, "question": "Are you aware of how many I have?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "aware", "of", "how", "many", "I", "have", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "WRB", "JJ", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 310, "answer": "You probably have 3, 4.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "probably", "have", "3", ",", "4", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 316, "question": "That's right?", "question_tokens": ["That", "'s", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 317, "answer": "It's been a phenomenon.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "been", "a", "phenomenon", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jack"]}, "docId": "131209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 329, "question": "Do you -- do you Tweet?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "--", "do", "you", "Tweet", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 330, "answer": "ARTOVI: I do and I think actually Jack is exactly the example of why we should be doing things like teaching computers and science in our schools.", "answer_tokens": ["ARTOVI", ":", "I", "do", "and", "I", "think", "actually", "Jack", "is", "exactly", "the", "example", "of", "why", "we", "should", "be", "doing", "things", "like", "teaching", "computers", "and", "science", "in", "our", "schools", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 338, "question": "Which should I be looking to get into?", "question_tokens": ["Which", "should", "I", "be", "looking", "to", "get", "into", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 339, "answer": "Code, programming.", "answer_tokens": ["Code", ",", "programming", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "TO", "."], "qSentId": 344, "question": "Well, you heard the man there, Jack Dorsey, who's now I think your billionaire, right, Jack?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "heard", "the", "man", "there", ",", "Jack", "Dorsey", ",", "who", "'s", "now", "I", "think", "your", "billionaire", ",", "right", ",", "Jack", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "RB", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "RB", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 345, "answer": "Not something I pay attention to.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "something", "I", "pay", "attention", "to", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jack Dorsey", "Jack"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "TO", "VB", "VBG", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "RB", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "WP", "POS", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 359, "question": "What do you think they should be doing here?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "they", "should", "be", "doing", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 360, "answer": "I think they are doing what they ought to be doing, which is they're taking a step back and they put the breaks on and they take -- they're taking a moment to decide what's the best thing to do for this huge production that they're right in the middle of.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "they", "are", "doing", "what", "they", "ought", "to", "be", "doing", ",", "which", "is", "they", "'re", "taking", "a", "step", "back", "and", "they", "put", "the", "breaks", "on", "and", "they", "take", "--", "they", "'re", "taking", "a", "moment", "to", "decide", "what", "'s", "the", "best", "thing", "to", "do", "for", "this", "huge", "production", "that", "they", "'re", "right", "in", "the", "middle", "of", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VBG", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "JJ", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "VBG", "IN", "DT", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "MD", "VB", ":", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 369, "question": "Is there an argument against it for that reason?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "there", "an", "argument", "against", "it", "for", "that", "reason", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 370, "answer": "I don't think there's any resistance to using computer graphics or visual effects to put heads on bodies or anything like that, but I think it really would be -- you couldn't really do that for the rest of the movie.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "there", "'s", "any", "resistance", "to", "using", "computer", "graphics", "or", "visual", "effects", "to", "put", "heads", "on", "bodies", "or", "anything", "like", "that", ",", "but", "I", "think", "it", "really", "would", "be", "--", "you", "could", "n't", "really", "do", "that", "for", "the", "rest", "of", "the", "movie", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 424, "question": "Has it helped you personally deal with the loss of your mother in such horrific circumstances to try and get on the frontfoot with this debate and get real change?", "question_tokens": ["Has", "it", "helped", "you", "personally", "deal", "with", "the", "loss", "of", "your", "mother", "in", "such", "horrific", "circumstances", "to", "try", "and", "get", "on", "the", "frontfoot", "with", "this", "debate", "and", "get", "real", "change", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 425, "answer": "It absolutely has.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "absolutely", "has", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["April"], "LOCATION": ["Connecticut", "New York", "Colorado"]}, "docId": "131209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "IN", "TO", "NN", "NN", "NN", "EX", "RB", "VBZ", "VBN", "NNS", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "JJ", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 430, "question": "How do you, as one of the families, one of the victims, feel about this?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", ",", "as", "one", "of", "the", "families", ",", "one", "of", "the", "victims", ",", "feel", "about", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "IN", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 431, "answer": "I mean as far as to changing gun law there definitely has been steps taken on the state level, you know, Connecticut, New York, Colorado for example, on a federal level absolutely disappointing what we saw in April.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", "as", "far", "as", "to", "changing", "gun", "law", "there", "definitely", "has", "been", "steps", "taken", "on", "the", "state", "level", ",", "you", "know", ",", "Connecticut", ",", "New", "York", ",", "Colorado", "for", "example", ",", "on", "a", "federal", "level", "absolutely", "disappointing", "what", "we", "saw", "in", "April", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 444, "question": "I mean in other words, do you think you have to go through this kind of this thing to really understand the horror of guns?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "in", "other", "words", ",", "do", "you", "think", "you", "have", "to", "go", "through", "this", "kind", "of", "this", "thing", "to", "really", "understand", "the", "horror", "of", "guns", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "RP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 445, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "DT", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", ":", "JJ", "NN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "``", "UH", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "JJ", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 452, "question": "It must bring back awful memories for you?", "question_tokens": ["It", "must", "bring", "back", "awful", "memories", "for", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 453, "answer": "After the initial shock and all of my flashbacks, (inaudible) my first thought is \"Oh God, how many?\"", "answer_tokens": ["After", "the", "initial", "shock", "and", "all", "of", "my", "flashbacks", ",", "(", "inaudible", ")", "my", "first", "thought", "is", "``", "Oh", "God", ",", "how", "many", "?", "''"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 473, "question": "Were you surprised at how incredibly brave she was?", "question_tokens": ["Were", "you", "surprised", "at", "how", "incredibly", "brave", "she", "was", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "WRB", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 474, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", ",", "CC", "VB", ",", "CC", "NN", ",", "CC", "NN", ",", "CC", "NNP", "NN", ",", "CC", "NN", ",", "CC", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 479, "question": "What else you didn't know?", "question_tokens": ["What", "else", "you", "did", "n't", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 480, "answer": "Hilarious, and perfect, and crazy, and smart, and well- spoken, and fierce, and tiny and she was the kind of mom, kind of principal that wouldn't yell at you.", "answer_tokens": ["Hilarious", ",", "and", "perfect", ",", "and", "crazy", ",", "and", "smart", ",", "and", "well-", "spoken", ",", "and", "fierce", ",", "and", "tiny", "and", "she", "was", "the", "kind", "of", "mom", ",", "kind", "of", "principal", "that", "would", "n't", "yell", "at", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Soto"]}, "docId": "131209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 486, "question": "How is the group doing collectively, given the remarkable attention that is received around the world?", "question_tokens": ["How", "is", "the", "group", "doing", "collectively", ",", "given", "the", "remarkable", "attention", "that", "is", "received", "around", "the", "world", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "RB", ",", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 487, "answer": "I have gotten extremely close with the Soto family.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "gotten", "extremely", "close", "with", "the", "Soto", "family", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 503, "question": "How was it for you that day?", "question_tokens": ["How", "was", "it", "for", "you", "that", "day", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 504, "answer": "I got married in the dress that my mom and I picked out at her house in the (inaudible) and the shoes that she would have tormented me for wearing.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "got", "married", "in", "the", "dress", "that", "my", "mom", "and", "I", "picked", "out", "at", "her", "house", "in", "the", "(", "inaudible", ")", "and", "the", "shoes", "that", "she", "would", "have", "tormented", "me", "for", "wearing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", ",", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "IN", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "RP", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "CC", "``", "JJ", "DT", "NNP", "''", "MD", "VB", "RP", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 512, "question": "Do you feel she's looking down and guiding you as you go on this or let this campaign now to try and make America a safer place?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "feel", "she", "'s", "looking", "down", "and", "guiding", "you", "as", "you", "go", "on", "this", "or", "let", "this", "campaign", "now", "to", "try", "and", "make", "America", "a", "safer", "place", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "CC", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "CC", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RB", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VB", "NNP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 513, "answer": "Every time I'm ready to give up, at school bus will drive by or I will be staring outside in the wind and my wind chimes will go off or I will see a butterfly in the blistering cold or \"Harriet the Spy\" will fall off my bookshelf.", "answer_tokens": ["Every", "time", "I", "'m", "ready", "to", "give", "up", ",", "at", "school", "bus", "will", "drive", "by", "or", "I", "will", "be", "staring", "outside", "in", "the", "wind", "and", "my", "wind", "chimes", "will", "go", "off", "or", "I", "will", "see", "a", "butterfly", "in", "the", "blistering", "cold", "or", "``", "Harriet", "the", "Spy", "''", "will", "fall", "off", "my", "bookshelf", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}]